Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Hollywood Bowl files, 1920-2014
  - Bound programs, 1972-1975 (Box 1,118, Folder 1-4)
  - Bound programs, 1976 (Box 1,119, Folder 1)
  - History files, 1922-2009 (Box 1,120, Folder 1-9)
  - Mrs. Leiland Atherton Irish files, 1920-1960 (Box 1,121, Folder 1-12)
  - Season files, 1922-1929 (Box 1,122, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1930-1934 (Box 1,123, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1935-1937 (Box 1,124, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1937-1940 (Box 1,125, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1940-1945 (Box 1,126, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1946-1950 (Box 1,127, Folder 1-7)
  - Season files, 1951-1956 (Box 1,128, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1956-1959 (Box 1,129, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1960-1962 (Box 1,130, Folder 1-7)
  - Season files, 1963-1965 (Box 1,131, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1965-1967 (Box 1,132, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1967-1969 (Box 1,133, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1969-1971 (Box 1,134, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1971-1973 (Box 1,135, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1973-1975 (Box 1,136, Folder 1-8)
  - Season files, 1975-1976 (Box 1,137, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1977-1978 (Box 1,138, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1978-1980 (Box 1,139, Folder 1-12)
  - Season files, 1980-1982 (Box 1,140, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1982-1983 (Box 1,141, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1983-1984 (Box 1,142, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1984-1986 (Box 1,143, Folder 1-13)
  - Season files, 1986-1987 (Box 1,144, Folder 1-12)
  - Season files, 1988-1989 (Box 1,145, Folder 1-12)
  - Season files, 1989-1990 (Box 1,146, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1990-1992 (Box 1,147, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1992-1993 (Box 1,148, Folder 1-7)
  - Season files, 1993-1995 (Box 1,149, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1995-1997 (Box 1,150, Folder 1-4)
  - Season files, 1996-1997 (Box 1,151, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1997-1998 (Box 1,152, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1998-1999 (Box 1,153, Folder 1-4)
  - Season files, 1999-2000 (Box 1,154, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 2000 (Box 1,155, Folder 1-3)
  - Season files, 2001 (Box 1,156, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2001-2002 (Box 1,157, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2002 (Box 1,158, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2002-2003 (Box 1,159, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 2004 (Box 1,160, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2005 (Box 1,161, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2005 (Box 1,162, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2006 (Box 1,163, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2006-2008 (Box 1,164, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 2008-2010 (Box 1,165, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 2010-2014 (Box 1,166, Folder 1-5)
  - Hollywood Bowl Association files, 1965-1986 (Box 1,167, Folder 1-22)
  - Hollywood Bowl Association files, 1965-1966 (Box 1,168, Folder 1-18)
  - Hollywood Bowl Association files, 1966-1971 (Box 1,169, Folder 1-15)
  - Photograph files, 1921-1938 (Box 1,170, Folder 1-111)
    Index tabs include the following: activities, performers, administrative personnel, and Mrs. Artie Mason Carter.
  - Photograph files, 1921-1929 (Box 1,171, Folder 1-124)
    Index tabs include the following: composers, conductors, construction, dancers, Easter Sunrise Services, and Alfred Hertz.
  - Photograph files, 1921-1934 (Box 1,172, Folder 1-124)
    Index tabs include the following: pianists, singers, support groups, views 1922-1931, and Women's World Peace Meeting 1921.
  - Photograph files, 1921-1966 (Box 1,173, Folder 1-138)
    This box contains the photograph collections of Mrs. Leiland Atherton Irish and John Orlando Northcutt.
  - Photograph files, 1921-1967 (Box 1,174, Folder 1-66)
    This box contains photographs from the John Orlando Northcutt collection, a ready reference historical file, and a "Bowl Volunteers" folder of images by Otto Rothschild.
  - Negative files, undated (Box 1,175, Folder 1-78)
  - Memorabilia, 1930-1996 (Box 1,176, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains a pendant, pin, postcards, Heifetz/Piatigorksy poster, a Bill Severns thank you card, certificates of appreciation for Mrs. Leiland Atherton Irish, a Karl Hubenthal "Culture Pearl" cartoon addressed to Bill Severns for the Bowl's 40th Anniversary, a scroll presented to Ernest Fleischmann in honor of the Bowl's 60th Anniversary season, a Magic of Mancini burlap bag, a Pilgrimage Play Spence Air Photo, a Hollywood Bowl Association resolution, two watercolor renderings, and a 1993 season promotional poster.
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1920-1937 (Box 1,177, Folder 1-28)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1937-1947 (Box 1,178, Folder 1-16)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1947-1949 (Box 1,179, Folder 1-24)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1949-1951 (Box 1,180, Folder 1-14)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1951-1957 (Box 1,181, Folder 1-16)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1958-1961 (Box 1,182, Folder 1-9)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, undated (Box 1,183, Folder 1-8)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1944-1959 (Box 1,184, Folder 1-11)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1957-1959 (Box 1,185, Folder 1-10)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1959-1960 (Box 1,186, Folder 1-11)
  - Pilgrimage Play files, 1961-1972 (Box 1,187, Folder 1-16)
  - Pilgrimage Play photographs, 1921-1948 (Box 1,188, Folder 1-147)
  - Pilgrimage Play photographs, 1921-1948 (Box 1,189, Folder 1-74)
    This box also contains three versions of the VHS The Hollywood Bowl: Music Under The Stars, dated 2000 and 2002.
  - Pilgrimage Play memorabilia, 1925-1957 (Box 1,190, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains Pilgrimage Play Association membership certificates, an Everyman Hollywood Bowl program, a scrapbook, a Mary Mother drawing, a map of the Pilgrimage Play property, and a Pilgrimage Play guest book signed by Earl Warren, Leo Carrillo, Roy Rogers, Dale Evans, Edward Roybal, Kenneth Hahn, and John Anson Ford.
  - 16mm film, undated (Box 1,191, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains three Gay Nineties at the Hollywood Bowl parts 1-3 films, a Hollywood Bowl Night color film, Fiesta Night at the Hollywood Bowl, and Viennese Night at the Hollywood Bowl, and a black and white Building of the Hollywood Bowl in the 1920s by mule film.
- Series 5: Los Angeles Civic Light Opera files, 1935-1998
  Edwin Lester was an American theatre director, impresario, and producer. He was the longtime general director of the Los Angeles Civic Light Opera (LACLO), which he founded in 1938. He also co-founded the LACLO's affiliate organization, the San Francisco Civic Light Opera (CLO), with Homer Curran in 1939.
  Source: Organizational history files, Box 1,192, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
  The Los Angeles Civic Light Opera files range in date from 1935-1998 and contain organizational history files; scripts and prompt books; season files; programs; scrapbooks; ad books; public relations files; San Francisco Civic Light Opera (CLO) ad books and programs; accounts payable files, window cards, photograph identification files; negatives; photographs; contact sheets; slides; Kenn Randall photographs; awards; proclamations; audio; and audiovisual materials.
  - Organizational history files, 1936-1985 (Box 1192, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains biographical information on Edwin Lester, organizational history of the LACLO, an inventory of his collection, an inventory of window cards, audition lists, clippings, obituaries, Lester tribute books, and production ephemera.
  - Scripts and prompt books, A-K, 1958-1985 (Box 1193, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains materials for Annie Get Your Gun to Kismet.
  - Scripts and prompt books, L-R, 1956-1970 (Box 1194, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains materials for Light Album Opera to Rosalinda.
  - Scripts and prompt books, S-Z, 1953-1969 (Box 1195, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains materials for The Song of Norway to Zorba, as well as a Dumas and Son conductor script.
  - The Great Waltz and The Merry Widow music manuscripts, undated (Box 1196, Folder 1-5)
  - Dumas and Son music manuscript, 1967 (Box 1197, Folder 1-2)
  - Zenda rewrite notes, 1963 (Box 1198, Folder 1-4)
  - Zenda music manuscript, 1963 (Box 1199, Folder 1)
  - Zenda lyric catalogue, 1938-1963 (Box 1200, Folder 1-4)
    This box also contains a Civic Light Opera chronological listing of productions, stars, and performers as well as vocal scores for Knickerbocker Holiday and The Merry Widow.
  - Showboat correspondence, music, and payroll, 1967 (Box 1201, Folder 1-3)
  - Showboat and At the Grand music manuscripts, undated (Box 1202, Folder 1-2)
  - Libretti, 1945-1958 (Box 1203, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains books for The Merry Widow, Damn Yankees, Guys and Dolls, Carousel, and The King and I.
  - Season files, 1935-1946 (Box 1204, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1947-1952 (Box 1205, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1953-1958 (Box 1206, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1959-1964 (Box 1207, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1965-1967 (Box 1208, Folder 1-14)
  - Season files, 1968-1969 (Box 1209, Folder 1-9)
  - Season files, 1970-1971 (Box 1210, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1972-1973 (Box 1211, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1974 (Box 1212, Folder 1-6)
  - Season files, 1975 (Box 1213, Folder 1-5)
  - Season files, 1976-1977 (Box 1214, Folder 1-11)
  - Season files, 1978-1980 (Box 1215, Folder 1-13)
  - Season files, 1981-1982 (Box 1216, Folder 1-10)
  - Season files, 1983-1985 (Box 1217, Folder 1-14)
  - Bound programs, 1983-1985 (Box 1218, Folder 1-3)
  - Season files, 1986-1987 (Box 1219, Folder 1-7)
  - Programs, The Act to Evita, 1967-1987 (Box 1220, Folder 1-24)
  - Programs, Fiddler to Joffrey, 1965-1984 (Box 1221, Folder 1-21)
  - Programs, The King and I to On Your Toes, 1965-1986 (Box 1222, Folder 1-23)
  - Programs, Pacific Overtures to The Sound of Music, 1945-1982 (Box 1223, Folder 1-21)
  - Programs, South Pacific to Zorba, 1966-1985 (Box 1224, Folder 1-18)
  - Souvenir programs, 1938-1969 (Box 1225, Folder 1-31)
  - Souvenir programs, 1938-1974 (Box 1226, Folder 1-61)
  - Scrapbooks, 1940-1941 (Box 1227, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1942-1943 (Box 1228, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook, 1944 (Box 1229, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1945-1946 (Box 1230, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1947 (Box 1231, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1948 (Box 1232, Folder 1-2)
    This box also contains a Magdalena scrapbook.
  - Scrapbooks, 1949-1950 (Box 1233, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1951-1952 (Box 1234, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook, 1953 (Box 1235, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1954-1955 (Box 1236, Folder 1-2)
    This box also contains a Peter Pan scrapbook.
  - Scrapbooks, 1955 (Box 1237, Folder 1-2)
    This box also contains a Kismet scrapbook.
  - Scrapbook, 1956 (Box 1238, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1957-1958 (Box 1239, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1959-1960 (Box 1240, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1961-1963 (Box 1241, Folder 1-3)
  - Ad books, 1949-1962 (Box 1242, Folder 1-14)
  - Ad books, 1963-1969 (Box 1243, Folder 1-8)
  - Ad books, 1970-1972 (Box 1244, Folder 1-8)
  - Ad books, 1973-1974 (Box 1245, Folder 1-7)
  - Ad books, 1975-1976 (Box 1246, Folder 1-8)
  - Ad books, 1977-1979 (Box 1247, Folder 1-8)
  - Ad books, 1977, 1980 (Box 1248, Folder 1-3)
    This box also contains taxi cab signs.
  - Public relations files, 1964-1977 (Box 1249, Folder 1-9)
    This box also contains Edwin Lester biographical materials and San Francisco Civic Light Opera files, and a manuscript edition of Rudolf Friml's musical composition, In the Spell of Night for the 1942 gala revival of The Vagabond King.
  - San Francisco CLO ad books, 1953-1972 (Box 1250, Folder 1-6)
  - San Francisco CLO ad books, 1973-1977 (Box 1251, Folder 1-5)
  - San Francisco CLO ad books, 1978-1980 (Box 1252, Folder 1-4)
  - San Francisco CLO souvenir programs, 1946-1975 (Box 1253, Folder 1-32)
  - Accounts payable files, 1978-1979 (Box 1254, Folder 1-3)
  - Window cards, The Act to Bells are Ringing, undated (Box 1255, Folder 1)
    This box also contains LACLO season window cards for the 32nd season through the 40th season. The 35th season is missing.
  - Window cards, Cabaret to Company, undated (Box 1256, Folder 1)
  - Window cards, Damn Yankees to 1491, undated (Box 1257, Folder 1)
  - Window cards, Guys and Dolls to Lovely Ladies, Kind Gentlemen, undated (Box 1258, Folder 1)
  - Window cards, Mack and Mabel to On Your Toes, undated (Box 1259, Folder 1)
  - Window cards, Pacific Overtures to Sweeney Todd, undated (Box 1260, Folder 1)
  - Window cards, Two Gentlemen of Verona to Zorba, undated (Box 1261, Folder 1)
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1262, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: The Act to Cat and the Fiddle, and artists: Charles Abbott to Max Bygraves.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1263, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: Cavalcade of Music to Fortune Teller, and artists: Sid Caesar to Wilbur Evans.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1264, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: 1491 to How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, and artists: Douglas Fairbanks, Jr. to Allan Gruet.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1265, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying to Lovely Ladies, and artists: Jester Hairston to Jack Kruschen.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1266, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: Mack and Mabel to Oliver, and artists: Fernando Lamas to Barbara Nunn.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1267, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: On a Clear Day You Can See Forever to Showboat, and artists: Pat O'Brien to Fran Ryan.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1268, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: Showboat to Vagabond King, and artists: David Sabin to Tito Vuolo.
  - Photograph identification file, undated (Box 1269, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards for productions: Walking Happy to Zorba, and artists: Charles Waldron, Jr. to George Zoritch.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1270, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for The Act to Bells are Ringing.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1271, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Blossom Time to Camelot.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1272, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Candide to Damn Yankees.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1273, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Dancin' to Flower Drum Song.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1274, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for 1491 to Gone With the Wind.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1275, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Good News to Half a Sixpence.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1276, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Hello Dolly to How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1277, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for I Do! I Do! to Kismet.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1278, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Kismet to Mack and Mabel.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1279, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Mame to Odyssey.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1280, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Odyssey to Pacific Overtures.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1281, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Pajama Game to Rosalinda.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1282, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains negatives for Rosalinda to The Sound of Music.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1283, Folder 1-136)
    This box contains negatives for South Pacific to Where's Charlie?
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1284, Folder 1-120)
    This box contains performance negatives: The Wiz to Zorba, and artist negatives: Walter Abel to Joyce Bryant.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1285, Folder 1-117)
    This box contains artist negatives: Henry Calvin to Richard Kiley.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1286, Folder 1-128)
    This box contains artist negatives: Lisa Kirk to Robert Rounseville.
  - Negatives, undated (Box 1287, Folder 1-57)
    This box contains artist negatives: Eileen Shawler to Gretchen Wyler.
  - Photographs, 1948-1977 (Box 1288, Folder 1-99)
    This box contains photographs: The Act to Annie Get Your Gun.
  - Photographs, 1958-1977 (Box 1289, Folder 1-87)
    This box contains photographs: Annie Get Your Gun to At the Grand.
  - Photographs, 1958-1979 (Box 1290, Folder 1-94)
    This box contains photographs: At the Grand to Bells are Ringing.
  - Photographs, 1938-1979 (Box 1291, Folder 1-112)
    This box contains photographs: Bells are Ringing to Broadbent.
  - Photographs, 1952-1977 (Box 1292, Folder 1-110)
    This box contains photographs: Broadbent to Camelot.
  - Photographs, 1963-1975 (Box 1293, Folder 1-93)
    This box contains Camelot photographs.
  - Photographs, 1945-1975 (Box 1294, Folder 1-89)
    This box contains photographs: Camelot to Carnival.
  - Photographs, 1953-1978 (Box 1295, Folder 1-106)
    This box contains photographs: Carnival to Chicago.
  - Photographs, 1950-1978 (Box 1296, Folder 1-121)
    This box contains photographs: Chicago to Coco.
  - Photographs, 1956-1979 (Box 1297, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Company to Destry Rides Again.
  - Photographs, 1952-1979 (Box 1298, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Destry Rides Again to Fanny.
  - Photographs, 1943-1974 (Box 1299, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Fanny to Firefly.
  - Photographs, 1946-1960 (Box 1300, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Flower Drum Song to The Fortune Teller.
  - Photographs, 1966-1969 (Box 1301, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: 1491 to George M!
  - Photographs, 1973 (Box 1302, Folder 1-190)
    This box contains Gigi photographs.
  - Photographs, 1973-1974 (Box 1303, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Gigi to Good News.
  - Photographs, 1949-1974 (Box 1304, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Good News to The Great Waltz.
  - Photographs, 1951-1965 (Box 1305, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Great Waltz to Guys and Dolls.
  - Photographs, 1951-1980 (Box 1306, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Guys and Dolls photographs.
  - Photographs, 1939-1980 (Box 1307, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Guys and Dolls to Hello Dolly.
  - Photographs, 1963-1967 (Box 1308, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Hello Dolly to How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
  - Photographs, 1963-1975 (Box 1309, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying photographs.
  - Photographs, 1968-1977 (Box 1310, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying to Irma La Douce.
  - Photographs, 1952-1977 (Box 1311, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Irma La Douce to The King and I.
  - Photographs, 1953-1974 (Box 1312, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The King and I to Kismet.
  - Photographs, 1953-1976 (Box 1313, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains Kismet photographs.
  - Photographs, 1949-1977 (Box 1314, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Kismet to Kiss Me Kate.
  - Photographs, 1964-1971 (Box 1315, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Kiss Me Kate to Knickerbocker.
  - Photographs, 1943-1971 (Box 1316, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Knickerbocker to Little Me.
  - Photographs, 1947-1974 (Box 1317, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Little Me to Mack and Mabel.
  - Photographs, 1948-1974 (Box 1318, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Mack and Mabel to Mame.
  - Photographs, 1940-1969 (Box 1319, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Mame to The Merry Widow.
  - Photographs, 1942-1961 (Box 1320, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Merry Widow to My Fair Lady.
  - Photographs, 1944-1972 (Box 1321, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: My Fair Lady to No, No, Nanette.
  - Photographs, 1959-1975 (Box 1322, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: No, No, Nanette to Oklahoma!
  - Photographs, 1959-1973 (Box 1323, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Oklahoma! to Oliver!
  - Photographs, 1973-1980 (Box 1324, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Oliver! to On a Clear Day You Can See Forever.
  - Photographs, 1964-1980 (Box 1325, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: On a Clear Day You Can See Forever to Pacific Overtures.
  - Photographs, 1940-1978 (Box 1326, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Pacific Overtures to Plain and Fancy.
  - Photographs, 1954-1974 (Box 1327, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Plain and Fancy to Porgy and Bess.
  - Photographs, 1938-1974 (Box 1328, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Porgy and Bess to Rosalinda.
  - Photographs, 1950-1972 (Box 1329, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Rosalinda to The Rothschilds.
  - Photographs, 1950-1972 (Box 1330, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Rothschilds to 1776.
  - Photographs, 1927-1967 (Box 1331, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Showboat to Silk Stockings.
  - Photographs, 1944-1962 (Box 1332, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Silk Stockings to Song of Norway.
  - Photographs, 1961-1978 (Box 1333, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Song of Norway to The Sound of Music.
  - Photographs, 1938-1978 (Box 1334, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Sound of Music to The Student Prince.
  - Photographs, 1966-1974 (Box 1335, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Student Prince to Sugar.
  - Photographs, 1947-1980 (Box 1336, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Sugar to Umbrellas of Cherbourg.
  - Photographs, 1942-1980 (Box 1337, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Umbrellas of Cherbourg to Where's Charlie?
  - Photographs, 1951-1977 (Box 1338, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Where's Charlie? to The Wiz.
  - Photographs, 1963-1977 (Box 1339, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: The Wiz to Zenda.
  - Photographs, 1963-1975 (Box 1340, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Zenda to Steven Arlen.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1341, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Sig Arno to Peter Brandon.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1342, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Charles Braswell to Bobby Clark.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1343, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Edmund Clark to Howard Deval.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1344, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Anthony Dexter to Eddie Foy, Jr.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1345, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Charlotta Frandsen to John Green.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1346, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Edward Greenberg to George S. Irving.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1347, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Walter Israel to Harold Lang.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1348, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Angela Lansbury to Jerry Mann.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1349, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: P.J. Mann to Mickey Morton.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1350, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Margot Moser to Irra Petina.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1351, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Alex Petrides to Anne Rogers.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1352, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs: Marti Rolph to Samuel and Bella Spewack.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1353, Folder 1-100)